Rockville Journal World War II Letters
Vernon Historical Society
Rockville Journal World War II Letters
1942-1946
Stephen Von Euw
10 linear feet
Vernon Historical Society
The collection contains letters, postcards, photographs, newsletters and mailing address information sent by local men and women in service during World War II to Stephen Von Euw, editor of The Rockville Journal in Rockville, Connecticut.
Restrictions
Collection open for research.
Acquisition Information
Ruth Von Euw, daughter of Stephen Von Euw left the collection of letters to the Vernon Historical Society upon her death in 2008.
Biography
Stephen Von Euw (1896-1955) was the editor of The Rockville Journal from the 1930s until his death. During World War II, Mr. Von Euw made sure that local servicemen and servicewomen received free copies of the paper wherever they were stationed. Many sent letters, postcards or other materials thanking him for giving them a link to home. Some shared their experiences whether stateside or on the front lines. Mr. Euw saved a letter from the government asking newspaper editors to collect materials from the War for posterity.
Scope and Content of Collection
The collection consists of folders for each military correspondent arranged alphabetically. With each folder, items are arranged chronologically. The amount of correspondence from each person varies. Those who knew Mr. Von Euw personally tended to write more. Some people only sent change of address forms as they moved from training to active duty. Photographs in the folders range from family pictures to portraits in uniform to snapshots in service to military publicity shots. Postcards show scenes from places in the US that were near training areas or pictures of base or airfields. Some postcards have scenes from overseas. A few postcards have cartoons depicting military life. Some soldiers sent newsletters from their units.
Arrangement
The collection of over 700 folders is stored in a five drawer file cabinet. The folders are alphabetically arranged. Materials with each folder are in chronological order.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
World War, 1939-1945- Connecticut- Rockville; World War, 1939-1945- Connecticut- Vernon; Von Euw, Stephen, 1896-1955; The Rockville Journal, Rockville, Connecticut; Correspondence; Photographs; Postcards; Military Newsletters
Separated Material
One box with 13 folders that contains materials and correspondence to and from Stephen Von Euw during World War II.
- Inventory
  - Aberle, Emil, Apr 08, 1944; Anzio; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Aborn, Christian G, Dec 10, 1943; APO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Aborn, Christian G, Oct 12, 1943; APO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Aborn, Christian G, Apr 22, 1944; New Caldonia; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Aborn, John J, Jun 01, 1945; Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Aborn, Christian G, undated; Tolland Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Aborn, Clarence E, undated; Tolland Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Aborn, Duane, May 14, 1945; Keesler Field,MS; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Aborn, Duane, May 02, 1945; Keesler Field,MS; Scenery; Tivoli Hotel, Biloxi, MS; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Aborn, Duane, Apr 03, 1943; Mrs Empson Aborn; Service Update, New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Aborn, Miles H, Oct 06, 1945; Mrs Fred M Aborn; Service Update; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Aborn, Christian G, Oct 05, 1945; Fort Oglethorpe; GA; Reassignment,Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Aborn, Clarence E, Dec 26, 1944; 8th Air Force; England; Received Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Abrahamson, Gayland, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Abrahamson, Gayland, Jan 26, 1945; Western Front; History of 101st Airborne; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Abrahamson, Gayland, May 13, 1944; Fort Benning; GA; Finished Paratroop School; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Ackerman, Ben, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Affricano, Benjamin E, Dec 09, 1945; Breman; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Affricano, Benjamin E, Nov 17, 1945; Kassel; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Affricano, Benjamin E, undated; Coventry Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Affricano, Benjamin E, Mar 20, 1945; Mrs Benjamin Affricano; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Affricano, Benjamin E, Dec 23, 1944; 6th Army; France; History of 397th Infantry; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  1
  - Albom, Milton J, undated; Pearl Harbor; HI; Coming Home; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Allen, Erwin, Jan 07, 1944; Carrier Aircraft Service; FPO San Francisco, CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Allen, Matthew P, Apr 13, 1945; Okinawa; Japan; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Allen, Matthew P, Oct 25, 1943; Camp Livingston; LA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Allen, Matthew P, Dec 09, 1944; APO San Francisco; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Allen, Erwin, Apr 28, 1905; Pacific; Military Record; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Alley, Malcolm R, Aug 02, 1943; Keesler Field,MS; Air Force; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Alley, Malcolm R, Nov 15, 1943; Fort Custer,MI; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Am, Fred, Jan 26, 1946; San Fransisco,CA; Camp Life; US Naval Training Center, "Treasure Island"; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Ambrosi, Bruno E, May 02, 1944; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Amende, Earl, undated; San Francisco; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Amende, Clayton, Nov 25, 1943; New Address, Emil AmEnde; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Amende, Clayton, Feb 17, 1944; New Address, Emil AmEnde; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Amende, Clayton, Jun 01, 1943; Sampson,NY; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Amende, Clayton, Oct 09, 1943; Sampson,NY; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Amprimo, Walter, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Amprimo, William, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Andrews, Roland C, May 15, 1944; Anzio; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Andrews, Russell E, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Andrews, Russell E, Jun 07, 1943; Sampson,NY; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Andrews, Dorothy E, Oct 25, 1945; Chickasha; OK; On Duty at Hospital; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Andrews, Roland C, undated; 7th Army; France; Description of Battle; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Andrews, Russell J, Feb 23, 1946; Boston; MA; Discharged, Miltary Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Archacki, Leon W., Dec 10, 1943; Mexia; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Archacki, Leon W., Dec 12, 1942; Seattle; WA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Archacki, Frank, Jul 13, 1943; North Africa; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Archacki, Leon W., May 27, 1945; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Archacki, Leon W., Dec 15, 1944; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Archacki, Leon W., Oct 15, 1944; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Archacki, Leon W., Aug 19, 1945; Camp Claiborn; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Archacki, Leon W, Oct 20, 1945; St Louis,MO; City Life; Municipal Auditorium; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Archacki, Leon W, Sep 10, 1943; Fort Custer,MI; City Life; Red Cross Building; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Archacki, Leon W, Sep 20, 1945; Fort Worth,TX; City Life; Texas Hotel; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Archacki, Leon W, Apr 24, 1944; Fort Eustis,VA; Newport News,VA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Archacki, Frank, Apr 17, 1943; Camp Sutton, NC; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Archacki, Peter J, Jan 31, 1946; Pearl Harbor; HI; Returning Home; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arens, Frederick J., Apr 18, 1944; San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arens, Frederick J., Oct 07, 1944; New Address, Mrs Raymond Clark; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arens, Frederick J., Sep 11, 1944; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arn, Frederick A., Apr 22, 1946; Treasure Island; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arn, Frederick A., Nov 02, 1945; Camp Parks; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arzt, Paul F., Dec 12, 1945; Reims; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arzt, Kenneth A, Sep 01, 1943; New Address; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arzt, Paul F., Jan 20, 1945; New Address, Marjorie Arzt; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arzt, Paul F., Dec 01, 1944; New Address, Marjorie Arzt; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arzt, Paul F., Nov 22, 1944; New Address, Marjorie Arzt; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arzt, Paul F., Oct 14, 1944; New Address, Marjorie Arzt; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arzt, Paul F., Sep 23, 1944; New Address, Marjorie Arzt; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arzt, Paul F., Apr 20, 1945; New Address, Marjorie Arzt; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arzt, Paul F., Jan 19, 1946; New Address, Marjorie Arzt; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Arzt, Paul F., Sep 18, 1945; New Address, Marjorie Arzt; PC-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Auridon, Clarence R, Oct 10, 1944; Brigham City; UT; Finished Hospital training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Avery, Charles F, Dec 30, 1944; Datona Beach; FL; In Hospital After Serving in Pacific; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Avery, Charles J, Oct 25, 1944; Boston; MA; On Furlough from South Pacific; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Babcock, Frederick H, May 17, 1944; Camp Stewart,GA; Camp Life; Savannah,GA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Babcock, Frederick H, Mar 27, 1944; Camp Stewart,GA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Babcock, Frederick H, Oct 16, 1944; Fort Jackson, SC; City Life; Public Library,Florence,SC; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backhaus, Richard E, Nov 09, 1944; Salinas; CA; Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Edwin, Oct 12, 1943; Birmingham; AL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Edwin, Mar 17, 1944; Santa Ana; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Ernest P, Mar 24, 1944; Santa Ana; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Edwin, Sep 27, 1943; Miami Beach; FL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Richard A, Nov 09, 1945; Frankfurt; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Edwin, Nov 01, 1945; Ota; Japan; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Edwin, Feb 22, 1941; Mitchell Field; Long Island NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Edwin, Aug 09, 1945; Fort Bragg; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Ernest P, Oct 25, 1944; Alamogordo; NM; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Frederick S., Jan 15, 1944; Newport; RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Frederick S., Sep 14, 1943; Newport; RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Frederick S., Sep 05, 1945; USS Lexington; Tokyo Bay; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Edwin F, Aug 26, 1943; Vernon Honor Roll; 55 Village Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Mary, Dec 08, 1944; Camp Gruber,OK; City Life; Muskogee,OK; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Richard A, Dec 02, 1944; Camp Gruber,OK; City Life; OK School for the Blind,Muskogee,OK; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Ernest P, May 31, 1945; Smoky Hill Field,KS; City Life; Salina,KS; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Edwin, Oct 18, 1943; Birmingham,AL; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Edwin, Oct 11, 1944; Camp Cooke,CA; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Edwin, Nov 03, 1941; Charlotte,NC; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Edwin, May 15, 1944; Monterey,CA; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Charles G, Jan 24, 1946; Manila; Philippines; Returning Home, Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Edwin F, Dec 27, 1945; 8th Army; Yokahama, Japan; Returning Home, Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Backofen, Walter A, Jul 29, 1946; Chicago; IL; Serving on Cruiser; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Badura, John A, Jun 05, 1946; Scott Field; IL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Badura, Robert, Mar 07, 1946; Scott Field; IL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Badura, Robert, Feb 20, 1946; Kessler Field; MS; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Badura, John A, Feb 07, 1945; Hawaii; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Badura, John A, Oct 14, 1944; Central Pacific; Awarded Badge; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Badura, John A, Jul 07, 1945; Pacific; Received Award; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A- De)
  - Baer, Karl W., Oct 19, 1944; Army Air Corp; NYC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baer, Raymond C, Jan 06, 1943; Fort Benning,GA; Camp Life; Infantry School Building; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baer, Karl W, Jul 20, 1945; 8th Air Force; England; On List of 8th AF after VE Day; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baer, Karl W, undated; 8th Air Force; Liberator Station,Engl; Armorer for B-24 Bomber Group; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bagdanowicz, Vito, Jan 01, 1945; Ellington Honor Roll; Killed in Action,France; Son of Mr and Mrs Victina Bagdanowicz; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bagnall, Charles I, May 19, 1945; Czechoslovakia; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bagnall, Charles I, May 18, 1945; Czechoslovakia; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bagnall, Charles I, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bagnall, Charles I, Oct 09, 1944; Camp Cooke,CA; Camp Cooke; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bagnall, Charles I, Apr 13, 1944; Fort Leonard Wood,MO; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bagnall, Charles I, Feb 05, 1944; Fort Collins,CO; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bagnall, Charles I, Jun 01, 1945; Info about Service; With Photo; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baker, PeterJ, Dec 20, 1944; Orona; ME; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baker, Percy W, Oct 22, 1944; APO 322; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baker, Percy W, Nov 14, 1943; South Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baker, Percy W, Mar 07, 1943; APO San Francisco; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baker, Percy W, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baker, Peter J, Jun 26, 1945; Northfield,VT; City Life; Norwich University; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baker, Percy W, Jul 09, 1945; Lake Placid,NY; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baker, Percy W, Jul 03, 1945; Lake Placid; NY; Returning Home, Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baldwin, Wilbert T, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baldwin, Wilbert N, undated; Luzon; Philippines; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Ballah, Martha, undated; Stafford Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bankowski, Steven, Apr 01, 1945; Luzon; Philippines; Involved in Recapture of Bataan,Corregidor; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barbaro, Alfred D, May 02, 1944; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barber, Fritz, May 15, 1944; Sampson,NY; Scenery; Seneca Lake, Geneva, NY; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barbero, Anne A, Oct 04, 1943; Fort Des Moines; IO; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barbero, Francis C, Feb 09, 1944; Sampson; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barbero, A. O., Jan 29, 1946; Virginia Beach; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barbero, A. O., Dec 19, 1944; Virginia Beach; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barbero, Alfred D, Mar 24, 1941; Vernon Honor Roll; 4 East Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barbero, John R, undated; San Fransisco,CA; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barbero, Anne A, undated; Manila; Philippines; Reunited with Army Husband; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barbero, Anne A, Aug 01, 1943; Fort Des Moines; Iowa; Completed Basic Training as WAC; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barbero, John R, undated; Manila; Philippines; Reunited with Army Wife; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barbero, John R, May 15, 1944; Bougainvlle; South Pacific; Awarded Badge; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barbero, John R, Jun 11, 1945; Philippines; Battle Description; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barbero, John R, Dec 02, 1944; Sothwest Pacific; Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bardini, Dominic, Feb 23, 1944; 6th Armored Division; Europe; Awarded Certificate; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bardini, George L, Apr 01, 1944; New Caledonia; South Pacific; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barisa, Chester J, Feb 02, 1945; 78th Infantry; Germany; Awarded Combat Badge; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leonard J, May 22, 1944; Service Update,Mrs L J Barrette; F-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leon G., Aug 06, 1945; USS Denver; Borneo; See Berrett, Leon G.; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leon G., Dec 13, 1945; USS Denver; w/ Enclosure; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leonard J., Jan 24, 1944; Fort Bragg; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leon G., Nov 10, 1945; USS Denver; Panama Canal; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leon G., Jul 04, 1945; USS Denver; Philippines; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leon G., Dec 13, 1944; USS Denver; w/ Enclosure; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leon G., Apr 09, 1945; USS Denver; w/ Enclosure; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leon G., Sep 22, 1945; Enclosure; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leon G., Nov 21, 1944; USS Denver; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leonard J., May 12, 1945; Okinawa; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leonard J., May 12, 1945; Okinawa; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leonard J., Nov 30, 1943; USS Denver; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leonard J., Aug 10, 1944; Guam; With Description of Invasion; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leon G., Apr 09, 1945; USS Denver; w/ Enclosure; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leon G, Apr 27, 1905; USS Denver; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leonard J, May 23, 1945; Vernon Honor Roll; Killed in Action,Okinawa; Age 25; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leonard J, May 25, 1944; San Diego,CA; Scenery; Border, USA and Tijuana, Mexico; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leonard J, Sep 18, 1944; Mrs Leonard Barrette; Received Combat Badge; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leonard J, Oct 20, 1944; Guam; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Barrette, Leonard J., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bartlett, Nelson W, Apr 11, 1944; Sampson,NY; City Life; Hobart College, Geneva, NY; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bartlett, Nelson W, May 02, 1944; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bascom, Robert E, undated; Somers Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baskowski, William S, Dec 02, 1944; Army Hospital; England; Recovering from Wound, Interview; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baskowski, William S, Jun 25, 1945; Berchtesgaden; Germany; Awarded Bronze Star; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bastek, Joseph, Apr 25, 1944; Vernon Honor Roll; 134 Union Street; Might be John Bastek; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bateman, Walter, Apr 21, 1944; Sampson; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bateman, Walter, Dec 03, 1944; Terminal Island; San Pedro CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bateman, Walter, Dec 18, 1945; USS Crenshaw; Tsingtao China; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bateman, Walter, Sep 30, 1945; Northern China; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bateman, Walter, Aug 16, 1946; South Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bateman, Walter, May 29, 1944; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baum, Lester, undated; San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baxter, Wilfred H, Feb 01, 1946; 8th Army, Fukuoka; Japan; Serving in Occupied Japan; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Baznall, Charles, Mar 12, 1944; Fort Leonard Wood,MO; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bedell, Frank E, Jun 01, 1945; Little Creek; VA; After Convoy Duty, Underwater Mines; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Belanger, John H, Aug 31, 1943; Wilmington, DE; Wilmington; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Belcher, George, Nov 03, 1945; Camp Swift; TX; History of 692nd Tank Destroyer Unit; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bell, Robert R, Mar 08, 1945; New Address; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bell, Robert R, Jun 14, 1945; New Address; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bell, Robert R, Jul 09, 1945; New Address; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bell, Robert R, Aug 23, 1945; Beavertail Point; Jamestown RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Bell, Robert, Jan 08, 1946; Beavertail Point; Jamestown RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Belotti, Joseph J., Jan 16, 1946; Bainbridge; MA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Belotti, Joseph J, May 05, 1943; Navy; 33 Windemere,Rockville; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Belotti, Joseph J, Sep 18, 1945; Norfolk; VA; Reported for Duty on a Destroyer; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Belotti, Joseph J, Jul 03, 1946; New York; NY; Released to Inactive Duty in Navy; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Belotti, Joseph J, Jun 01, 1945; Great lakes; IL; Commissioned as Ensign; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Benoit, William J, May 20, 1945; 8th Air Force; England; On List of 8th AF after VE Day; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Benson, Charles, Oct 09, 1944; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)
  - Benson, Charles, May 07, 1945; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder A-De)